hitwebdesign.com 2013-08-27

# Heritage Internet Technologies

  | 

**  
Privacy Policy**      

**  
Our Commitment To Privacy:**  
Your privacy is important to Heritage™ Web Design, LLC and its legal successors and assigns. Heritage may do business under the names Heritage ™ Internet Technologies or HIT Web Design (HIT) among others. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining how HIT treats personal information that HIT collects and receives. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our website and where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**The Information We Collect:**  
This notice applies to personal information collected or submitted on HIT websites that is not otherwise publicly available. In general you can view or visit HIT pages without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself.

On some of our web pages Clients can order products and make requests. The types of personal information collected from these pages include, but is not be limited to:

Name  
Address  
Email Address   
Phone Number  
IP Address

Upon purchasing HIT products or services we may collect additional personal information including, but not limited to:

Credit Card number  
Account Number  
Bank Account Information  
Any combination of personal information that could be used to determine identity

**The Way We Use Information:**  
We use the information the Client provides when placing an order to complete that order and to provide the services requested. Personal contact information is provided to domain name provider and other third party service providers. ICANN requires domain name providers to make contact information or “WHOIS” information related to the registration of domain names public, including your name, address, phone number, fax number, email address. 

We use email addresses to answer the email we receive. We use email addresses provided as personally identifiable information to communicate with you regarding your account.   
By providing your telephone number you agree that this constitutes an inquiry, application or purchase for purposes of telemarketing laws and you agree to receive future information about products and services us for us regardless of if your telephone and/or cell phone number is on the Federal Do Not Call List or State No Dot Call List.

**Tracking and Cookies**  
Our web pages may utilize “cookies” and other tracking technology to enhance your online experiences and to learn about the way you use HIT services in order to improve the quality of HIT services. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them.

HIT Servers automatically record information when you visit our websites or use HIT products or services, accept our TOS, or submit content, including the URL, IP address, browser software, operating system types, clickstream patterns and the date and time.

**Third Parties**  
We reserve the right to send you certain communications regarding HIT Services, and some third party services, related to your HIT Account, without offering you the opportunity to opt out.

It is Clients responsibility to check the privacy policy of third parties before submitting any personal information to a third party site.

HITWEBDESIGN.COM ASSUMES NO RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY FOR THEFT, LOSS, ALTERATION OR MISUSE OF PERSONAL OR OTHER INFORMATION LAWFULLY PROVIDED BY HITWEBDESIGN.COM TO THIRD PARTIES, OR WITH REGARD TO THE FAILURE OF ANY THIRD PARTY TO ABIDE BY THIS PRIVACY NOTICE OR SUCH THIRD PARTY'S PRIVACY POLICY OR ANY AGREEMENT BETWEEN THAT THIRD PARTY AND HITWEBDESIGN.COM

**Websites Other than Hitwebdesign.com**  
Hitwebdesign.com has no control or responsibility for websites that may be linked to Hitwebdesign.com or for third party websites, or for their security or privacy policies. It is Clients responsibility to check the privacy policy of each website before submitting personal information.

**Information Sharing**  
We may share information with third parties in limited circumstances including if required to do so by law or in a good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with legal processes or governmental requests, regulatory requests, including ICANN, and DMCA takedown notices, enforce the TOS, provide customer service, protect the rights, property or safety of HIT and the public, or to prevent, detect or otherwise address fraud, illegal activities, security or technical issues.

We do not share the personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to our services or as otherwise described in this policy without also providing you with an opportunity for opt-in consent.   
We may use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we do not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

**Business Transfer**  
If HIT subcontracts services, assigns transfers or sells ongoing servicing or hosting of Client account the Clients account and customer information will be shared with any successor entity.

**Our Commitment to Data Security** :  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure your personal information. We restrict access to personal information to those with the need to know that information in order to provide services.

**Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy:**  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, HIT does not collect or maintain information from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of HIT websites, products or services are structured to attract anyone under 13. 

**Accessing and Updating Personal Information:**  
When contacting HIT we make a good faith effort to provide Clients with access to Clients personal information and either to update it or delete it, if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purpose. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information to be accessed, updated or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonable, or require disproportionate technical effort.

**Changes:**  
This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. Changes will be posted on our website. Each version of this Policy will include an effective date and we will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy available.

**How to Contact Us**  
Should you have any other questions, concerns or complaints about our Privacy Policy please email us at [ Privacy@hitwebdesign.com](mailto:Privacy@hitwebdesign.com)  You may also submit updates and corrections about your personal information to [ Privacy@hitwebdesign.com](mailto:Privacy@hitwebdesign.com)

©2007 HIT  

|    
---|---|---
